<changelog>
	<changes>
		<version>1.6.4</version>
		<change>
      ANDROID: Fire Stick & Fire TV remote overrides gamepad port 0 on button press and viceversa like SHIELD devices
      ANDROID: Provide default save / system / state / screenshot locations
      AUDIO: Audio mixer supports MOD/S3M/XM file types now!
      INPUT: input swap override flag (for remotes) is cleared correctly
      INPUT: allow specifying libretro device in remap files
      INPUT: allow specifying analog dpad mode in remap files
      INPUT: allow saving libretro device to remap files
      INPUT: allow saving analog dpad mode to remap files
      INPUT: allow removing core and game remap files from the menu
      COMMON: Cores can now request to set a ‘shared context’. You no longer need to explicitly enable ‘Shared Hardware Context’ for Citra/OpenLara/Dolphin.
      COMMON: Add ‘Delete Core’ option to Core Information menu.
      COMMON: Allow Max Timing Skew to be set to 0.
      COMMON: Change the “content dir” behavior so it works on either a flag or an empty directory setting, now platform drivers can provide defaults for save / system / state / screenshot dirs and still allow the content dir functionality, these settings are under settings / saving and flagged as advanced
      GUI: You can turn on/off ‘Horizontal Animation’ now for the XMB menu. Turning animations off can result in a performance boost.
      GUI: Fix sublabel word-wrapping in XMB where multi-byte languages were cut off too soon
      LOCALIZATION: Update Dutch translation
      LOCALIZATION: Update Traditional Chinese translation
      LOCALIZATION: Update Italian translation
      LOCALIZATION: Update Russian translation
      WINDOWS: Provide default save / system / state / screenshot locations
      LOBBIES: Show what country the host is in
      MENU: Enable OSD text rendering for gdi and libcaca drivers
      WINDOWS 98/ME/2K: Set default directory for MSVC 2005 RetroArch version.
      WII: Better V-Sync handling, backported from SuperrSonic.
      WIIU: Exception handler rewritten.
    </change>
	</changes>
</changelog>
